

LE CHI HAI

FRONTEND - DEVELOPER

16/07/2001

- Male
- **** 0376782528
- chihaile4b@gmail.com
- ▼ Tan Binh , Tp.HCM
- i facebook.com/mi.yu.5682944/

SUMMARY

With good pedagogical skill along with knowledge such as Scratch, Web, GameMaker. I have 1 year of experience in teaching for student from level 1 to level 3. I have 3 month of experience with role intern Frontend - Developer in website development and programing.

OBJECTIVE

Apply programming experience and understanding of the information technology industry to become a professional programmer, bringing a lot of value to the company.

SKILL

HTML, CSS, SASS/SCSS, JS

Proficient at a good level

Framework

ReactJS, ReactJS - Typescript

Redux, redux-toolkit, reduxthunk

Proficient at a good level

Framework - styles

Material UI, Ant Design, TailwindCSS

Database

MongoDB, Firebase

EDUCATION

HCMC UNIVERSITY OF EDUCATION

10/2019 - NOW

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY / SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGY

GVA: 3.1/4

EXPERIENCE

MINDX TENOLOGY

06/2022 - 03/2023

Mentor

- Support teaching student with subjects such as Scratch, Web, GameMaker. ...
- Set up contents for each lesson according to the right program.
- Mark students' homework each week
- Evaluate each student's learning level through the end-ofcourse project.

ALTA SOFTWARE

03/2023 - 05/2023

Intern Frontend - Developer

- Trainning by trainer and working with the team and individual
- Learning apply knowledge typescript into projects to make sure data match because typescript always requires declaring the data before binding
- Handing connect mongoDB into server NodeJS and create controller handle routes
- Using redux, redux-toolkit, redux-thunk for processing data as well as asynchronous processing
- Processing tasks according to the format of project CMS Admin Page

PROJECTS

ECOMMERCE

02/2022 - 03/2022

Frontend

- Process authentication with feature authentication of Firebase: login, logout, register account.
- Process loading data from store redux to components when get API by axios.
- Process add products to cart and pay for your order by redux, redux-toolkit. View products by options such as electronic, clothing, jewelery
- View information product such as color, quantity, comment,

Office Information

Word, Excel, Powerpoint

Tools

Git, GitHub, VS Code, Visual Studio Code

English

Reading comprehension, listening at a basic level

INTEREST

Prefer to travel, go on a motorbike trip with friends

I love watching movies and playing games

evaluation...

Link Github: https://github.com/lehai4/ecommerce Link web: https://ecommerce-lehai4.vercel.app/

TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION

Firebase, yup, formik, redux, redux-toolkit, axios, SCSS, CLSX

CMS - TICKET - SALSE

03/2023 - 04/2023

Frontend

- Process loading data from store redux to components when get data from firebase by redux-toolkit.
- Process show chart & filter data by options
- Process add and update data

Link Github: https://github.com/lehai4/cMS-ticket-sale

Link web: https://c-ms-ticket-sale.vercel.app/

TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION

React-typescript, redux, redux-toolkit, SCSS, tailwindCSS, react-modal, react-data-table, react-datepicker, chart.js, @mui, firebase, moment

QUEUING - SYSTEM

04/2023 - 05/2023

Frontend - Backend

- Backend:
 - Set up server according to model MVC
- Set up environment, schema mongo and connect toward mongoDB
- Create model controller for process router register, login, logout, update, delete
- Frontend:
- Process login, logout, register, forget-password and change password account
 - Process show chart & filter data by options
 - Process add, update and detail data
 - Process download file(.pdf)
- Process change role, add role, add account, update account, update profile image
 - Process recording of user action history

Link Github: https://github.com/lehai4/queuing-system

TECHNOLOGY DESCRIPTION

- Backend: NodeJs, ExpressJS, JWT, MongoDB
- Frontend: react-typescript, @mui, redux, redux-toolkit, chart.js, react-datepicker, axios, firebase, formik, yup, jwt-decode, react-modal, moment, SCSS, tailwindCSS

CERTIFICATE

TOEIC 2023

Infomatics Certificate 2020

© 123job.vn